Parapsychology Laboratory Records, 1893-1984
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Research Files Series, 1912-1917and 1937-1963, 235 containers (117.5 lin. ft.)
  - Experimenter Files, 1912-1965
    - Pratt, J.G.
      - Humphrey-Pratt comparison of test procedures, 1941, (2 folders) (Box 503)
      - Rhine-Stuart butter and eggs precognition experiment, 1941 (Box 503)
      - Russell-Pratt GESP study, 1941 (Box 503)
      - Agnes Snyder precog, 1941-1942, (3 folders) (Box 503)
      - McMahan 3-turn data, c. 1945-1946 (Box 504)
      - Token object tests, 1945-1948, (21 folders) (Box 504)
      - Token-object tests, 1945-1948, (13 folders) (Box 505)
      - Token-object tests, 1945-1948, (4 folders) (Box 506)
      - Birdrim displacement papers, 1946, (3 folders) (Box 506)
      - Lawfulness of position effects, 1946, (2 folders) (Box 506)
      - Burke Smith grouping studies, 1946, (3 folders) (Box 506)
      - Gibson exploratory PK, 1946-1948 (Box 507)
      - Cranmore-Pratt PK exp't, 1947, (4 folders) (Box 507)
      - Gibson Dave Dean Communications, 1947 (Box 507)
      - Bob Langen DT data, 1947 (Box 507)
      - McMahan-Pratt precog. experiment, 1947 (Box 507)
      - Pratt-Cammaack PK study, 1947, (2 folders) (Box 507)
      - Reeves PK position effects, 1947 (Box 507)
      - Reeves PK tests, 1947 (Box 507)
      - Restricted success in PK, 1947, (2 folders) (Box 508)
      - Riess series analyses, 1947 (Box 508)
      - Sanderson material, 1947, (6 folders) (Box 508)
      - Target preference study, 1947, (2 folders) (Box 508)
      - Trial-by-trial analyses, 1947 (Box 508)
      - Cranmore long-distance GESP, 1947-1948, (2 folders) (Box 508)
      - Gibson placement PK, 1947-1951 (Box 508)
      - Gibson placement PK, 1947-1951, (4 folders) (Box 509)
      - Cox-Pratt distance PK, 1948 (Box 509)
      - D.J. West token object tests, 1948 (Box 509)
      - Hornaday-Scherer PK experiment, 1948 (Box 509)
      - McMahan “PK” experiment, 1948 (Box 509)
      - Miscellaneous data, 1948 (Box 509)
      - Miscellaneous data, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 510)
      - Miscellaneous record sheets, 1948, (3 folders) (Box 510)
      - Precognitive drawings, 1948 (Box 510)
      - STM experiment, 1948 (Box 510)
      - Hand-picture token object tests, 1948-1949, (2 folders) (Box 510)
      - Rose PK data, 1948-1949 (Box 510)
      - Rose PK data, 1948-1949 (Box 511)
      - Cox-Pratt correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 511)
      - Cox PK placement, 1948-1950 (Box 511)
      - Mary Buirgy ESP, 1949 (Box 511)
      - Change-of-call analyses, 1949, (6 folders) (Box 511)
      - Change-of-call analyses, 1949, (6 folders) (Box 512)
      - Rose Aborigines paper, 1949-1951, (4 folders) (Box 512)
      - Jessup ESP test, 1950, (4 folders) (Box 512)
      - Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 512)
      - Lab letters to be answered, 1949 (Box 513)
      - Miscellaneous data, 1949 (Box 513)
      - Cadoret-Pratt consistent missing, 1949-1950, (5 folders) (Box 513)
      - Cormack placement PK, 1949-1951, (2 folders) (Box 513)
      - Miscellaneous data, 1949-1951 (Box 513)
      - Raleigh series, 1950, (6 folders) (Box 514)
      - Repeated calling, 1950 (Box 514)
      - Rose Hexagon experiment, 1950 (Box 514)
      - Forwald placement PK, 1950-1951, (3 folders) (Box 514)
      - Willys-Pratt distance series, 1950-1951, (2 folders) (Box 515)
      - May Bell paper, 1951 (Box 515)
      - Correspondence pending, 1951 (Box 515)
      - Direction finding experiments, 1951 (Box 515)
      - Rivers home tests, 1951 (Box 515)
      - Roanoke talk on displacement, 1951 (Box 515)
      - Hallet miscellaneous data, 1951 (Box 515)
      - Hallet multiple aspect ESP, 1951, (4 folders) (Box 515)
      - Hallet predictive test, 1951, (3 folders) (Box 516)
      - Hallet single call experiment, 1951 (Box 516)
      - Call sequence and ESP, c. 1951-1952 (Box 516)
      - Migration and Orientation reprints, 1951-1960 (Box 516)
      - Cormack new series, 1951-1952 (Box 516)
      - Homing correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 516)
      - Homing records, 1951-1952, (2 folders) (Box 516)
      - Statistics, 1952 (Box 516)
      - Taylor machine data, 1952 (Box 516)
      - Van de Castle clairvoyance experiment, 1952 (Box 516)
      - ARPW homing correspondence, 1951-1953, (2 folders) (Box 517)
      - Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 517)
      - Marsh paper, 1952-1953 (Box 517)
      - Cox placement PK, 1952-1954 (Box 517)
      - Homing records, 1952-1958, (9 folders) (Box 517)
      - Homing records, 1952-1958, (26 folders) (Box 518)
      - Homing records, 1952-1958, (18 folders) (Box 519)
      - Homing records, 1952-1958, (8 folders) (Box 520)
      - Correspondence, 1953 (Box 520)
      - Forwald placement PK, 1953-1954 (Box 520)
      - Forwald placement PK, 1953-1954 (Box 521)
      - Homing records, 1953-1954, (18 folders) (Box 521)
      - Homing records, 1953-1954, (11 folders) (Box 522)
      - Night-flying correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 522)
      - Homing records, 1953-1956, (5 folders) (Box 522)
      - Homing records, 1953-1956 (Box 523)
      - Homing writings, 1953-1958, (11 folders) (Box 523)
      - Homing writings, 1953-1958, (6 folders) (Box 524)
      - ONR records, 1953-1961, (4 folders) (Box 524)
      - CIBA Foundation symposium, 1964 (Box 524)
      - Wallin PK experiment, 1954, (3 folders) (Box 524)
      - Wallin PK experiment, 1954, (2 folders) (Box 525)
      - Mangan flower experiment, 1954-1955, (4 folders) (Box 525)
      - Cadiret ESP application, 1955, (2 folders) (Box 525)
      - Mangan subject motivation test, 1955, (2 folders) (Box 525)
      - Reprints received, 1955, (2 folders) (Box 525)
      - Reprints received, 1955 (Box 526)
      - Vasse 1st grade ESP, 1955-1956, (2 folders) (Box 526)
      - Wilburn-Mangan placement PK, 1955-1956, (2 folders) (Box 526)
      - Meier radiesthesia correspondence, 1955-1960 (Box 526)
      - Marsh thesis abstract, 1956 (Box 526)
      - Reprints received, 1956 (Box 526)
      - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 526)
      - Forwald Duke PK, 1957 (Box 526)
      - Forwald Duke PK, 1957 (Box 527)
      - Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 527)
      - Peggy Murphy placement PK, 1957 (Box 527)
      - Pohl PK experiment, 1957-1959, (4 folders) (Box 527)
      - Alabama fire case, 1958 (Box 527)
      - Forwald placement PK, 1958, (2 folders) (Box 527)
      - Herrmann correspondence, 1958, (2 folders) (Box 527)
      - Herrmann correspondence, 1958, (8 folders) (Box 528)
      - Herrmann correspondence, 1958, (5 folders) (Box 529)
      - House of Flying Objects, 1958, (4 folders) (Box 529)
      - House of Flying Objects, 1958, (2 folders) (Box 530)
      - ISPK file, 1958 (Box 530)
      - Mundy-Castle paper, 1958 (Box 530)
      - Notes on parapsychology, science and religion, 1958 (Box 530)
      - RSPK questionnaire, 1958 (Box 530)
      - Seaford poltergeist case, 1958 (Box 530)
      - Blake GESP trials, 1959 (Box 530)
      - Control over ESP, 1959 (Box 530)
      - Bill Cox S-C-S experiment, 1959, (4 folders) (Box 530)
      - Hurkos baseball predictions, 1959 (Box 530)
      - Marabini paper, 1959 (Box 530)
      - Physicality and psi, 1959 (Box 530)
      - Precognitive dream experiment, 1959 (Box 530)
      - Turner paper, 1959 (Box 530)
      - VanderJagt paper, 1959 (Box 530)
      - Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 531)
      - Pisciotta clairvoyance series, 1959-1960 (Box 531)
      - Experimental memo book, 1959-1960 (Box 531)
      - Louwerens school experiment, 1959-1961 (Box 531)
      - Miscellaneous, 1959-1963 (Box 531)
      - Ryal papers, 1959-1963, (7 folders) (Box 531)
      - Attitudes and ESP, 1960 (Box 531)
      - Call-write data, 1960, (2 folders) (Box 531)
      - Case for PK, 1960 (Box 531)
      - Interpsychical contact, 1960 (Box 531)
      - LD DT with Hubert Pearce, 1960 (Box 531)
      - Peggy Murphy experiment, 1960 (Box 532)
      - Perot PK experiments, 1960 (Box 532)
      - Saleh relaxation protocol, 1960 (Box 532)
      - Peggy Murphy correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 532)
      - Saleh clairvoyance data, 1960-1961 (Box 532)
      - Sanders call-write precognition, 1960-1961, (8 folders) (Box 532)
      - Sanders call-write precognition, 1960-1961, (7 folders) (Box 533)
      - Sanders call-write precognition, 1960-1961, (7 folders) (Box 534)
      - Van Busschbach American work, 1960-1961 (Box 534)
      - Weisman school experiment, 1960-1961, (3 folders) (Box 534)
      - Byrnes school test, 1961 (Box 535)
      - Freeman Jr. High test, 1961, (3 folders) (Box 535)
      - Hansel affair, 1961, (7 folders) (Box 535)
      - Hansel affair, 1961, (2 folders) (Box 536)
      - Perot ESP paper, 1961 (Box 536)
      - Pratt-Birge method letters, 1961 (Box 536)
      - Radio animal tracking conference, 1961 (Box 536)
      - Raleigh NCPA symposium, 1961 (Box 536)
      - Ratte PK, 1961 (Box 536)
      - Rolling school test, 1961 (Box 536)
      - Raymond Russell paper, 1961 (Box 536)
      - Sandos subception paper, 1961 (Box 536)
      - Weisman school precognition test, 1961, (12 folders) (Box 536)
      - Chris Wood keys, 1961 (Box 536)
      - Chauvin papers, 1961-1962, (3 folders) (Box 537)
      - Kenneth Tenny experiments, 1961-1962, (12 folders) (Box 537)
      - Kenneth Tenny experiments, 1961-1962, (8 folders) (Box 538)
      - Shields children experiment, 1961-1962 (Box 538)
      - Banerjee series 6 and 14, 1962 (Box 539)
      - Freeman ESP trials, 1962 (Box 539)
      - Parapsychology/Communist Europe, c. 1962 (Box 539)
      - Prasad reprints, 1962 (Box 539)
      - Jobling correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 539)
      - W.E. Cox materials, 1962-1965 (Box 539)
      - Anpsi bibliography, undated (Box 539)
      - Foster summary of dog work, undated (Box 539)
      - Game room, undated (Box 539)
      - Greene thyroid experiment, undated (Box 539)
      - Herring notes, undated (Box 539)
      - Lancaster game, undated (Box 539)
      - McMahan notes, undated (Box 539)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 539)
      - Miscellaneous data, undated, (3 folders) (Box 539)
      - Miscellaneous data, undated, (4 folders) (Box 540)
      - Murphy Psi-Chek game, undated (Box 540)
      - Notes on dowsing, undated (Box 540)
      - Pegram ESP trials, undated (Box 540)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 540)
      - Piano music, undated (Box 540)
      - Review of Carrington, undated (Box 540)
      - Rose book manuscript, undated (Box 540)
      - Reversible figures, undated (Box 540)
      - Rhine notes, undated (Box 540)
      - JBR-LER position effect analyses, undated (Box 540)
      - Pratt-Woodruff cross-check date, undated (Box 540)
      - Statistics, undated (Box 540)
      - Supply ministers test, undated (Box 540)
      - Word association tests, undated (Box 540)
    - Rao, K. Language performance test (Box 540)
    - Reeves, M.
      - ESP and IQ, 1938 (Box 540)
      - PK lag effect, 1945-1946 (Box 540)
      - High-low dice, 1948 (Box 540)
    - Reichenberg Gratification and ESP, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 541)
    - Rhine, J.
      - Notes on “Lady,” 1927-1928 (Box 541)
      - Notes and experimental records, 1929-1931 (Box 541)
      - Frick experimental data, 1930, (4 folders) (Box 541)
      - Laboratory notebook, 1930-1933 (Box 541)
      - Pratt data books (C-31), 1932-1933 (Box 541)
      - Work with Hubert Pearce (C-33), 1932-1933 (Box 541)
      - Pearce-Pratt distance series (C-29), 1933, (2 folders) (Box 541)
      - Pearce-Pratt-Rhine DBT (C-29a), 1933 (Box 542)
      - Rhine-Ownbey distance ESP, 1933 (Box 542)
      - Louisa Rhine ESP, 1934 (Box 542)
      - Work with Eileen Garrett, 1934 (Box 542)
      - Three-run decline data, 1935 (Box 542)
      - Mühl LD experiment, 1935-1936, (9 folders) (Box 542)
      - Drug studies, 1935-1939, (3 folders) (Box 542)
      - Drug studies, 1935-1939, (7 folders) (Box 543)
      - Current ESP data (D-25), 1936 (Box 543)
      - Distance ESP summary book, 1936 (Box 543)
      - Burke Smith papers, 1936 (Box 543)
      - McLaughlin experiment forms, c. 1937 (Box 543)
      - Miscellaneous, 1937 (Box 543)
      - Data summaries, 1937-1938 (Box 544)
      - Pratt-Woodruff keys, 1938 (Box 544)
      - Burke Smith misc., 1938-1941 (Box 544)
      - Miscellaneous data, 1938-1942, (4 folders) (Box 544)
      - Roll box data, 1939 (Box 544)
      - Siegel shock experiment, 1939 (Box 544)
      - Seawall experiment at Wright Refuge, 1940 (Box 544)
      - 6700 series scores, 1939 (Box 544)
      - Clark-Pratt precognition experiment, 1941, (2 folders) (Box 545)
      - Classroom ESP tests, 1941, (4 folders) (Box 545)
      - ESP test instructions, c. 1941 (Box 545)
      - Gardner twin GESP, 1941 (Box 545)
      - PK decline analyses, 1941? (Box 545)
      - Rhine-Humphrey terminal salience, 1941 (Box 545)
      - Rhine-Humphrey terminal salience, 1941, (3 folders) (Box 546)
      - Rhine-Humphrey salience ratios, 1941-1942, (8 folders) (Box 546)
      - Rhine-Humphrey salience ratios, 1941-1942, (16 folders) (Box 547)
      - Rhine-Humphrey salience ratios, 1941-1942, (12 folders) (Box 548)
      - Statistics group, 1941-1942 (Box 548)
      - Detroit PK study, 1942 (Box 548)
      - Insurance, 1942 (Box 548)
      - Pratt notes on criticism, c. 1942 (Box 548)
      - PK trials, 1942-1943, (3 folders) (Box 548)
      - PK analyses, 1942-1944, (7 folders) (Box 549)
      - Student tests, 1942-1944, (4 folders) (Box 549)
      - Humphrey paper, 1943 (Box 549)
      - Rile-Moskowitz experiment, 1943 (Box 549)
      - Current PK work, 1943-1944, (2 folders) (Box 549)
      - D.J. West data, 1944 (Box 549)
      - Zenith tests, 1944, (6 folders) (Box 550)
      - QD analyses, 1944, (7 folders) (Box 550)
      - Anna Rochlin data, 1944-1945 (Box 550)
      - Garrett sittings, 1945 (Box 550)
      - PK data, 1945-1946 (Box 550)
      - PK manuscripts, 1945-1947 (Box 551)
      - Burke Smith PK data, 1946, (2 folders) (Box 551)
      - Humphrey “clicker” series, 1946, (2 folders) (Box 551)
      - Humphrey “Degree of success” experiment, 1946 (Box 551)
      - Santo Domingo tests, 1947 (Box 551)
      - Dakota-Wesleyan-S. Dakota ESP Series, 1948, (2 folders) (Box 552)
      - Garrett precognition trials, 1948 (Box 552)
      - Humphrey ESP experiment, 1948 (Box 552)
      - Reeves drawing experiment, 1948-1949, (2 folders) (Box 552)
      - Greene Olivet College ESP, 1949 (Box 552)
      - Gibson light vs. heavy dice, 1951 (Box 552)
      - LER-JBR round vs. square dice, 1951 (Box 553)
      - Alice Buck distance precog., 1952-1955, (3 folders) (Box 553)
      - Dynes race predictions, 1953 (Box 553)
      - Ratte-Green Camp Kirkwald experiments, 1956-1957, (3 folders) (Box 553)
      - Ratte-Greene Camp Kirkwald experiments, 1956-1957, (6 folders) (Box 554)
      - Gerding color telepathy, 1957, (2 folders) (Box 554)
      - Gerding LD GESP, 1957, (4 folders) (Box 555)
      - Classroom ESP data, 1957-1958, (2 folders) (Box 555)
      - Classroom ESP data, 1957-1958, (6 folders) (Box 556)
      - Classroom ESP data, 1957-1958, (7 folders) (Box 557)
      - Classroom ESP data, 1957-1958, (7 folders) (Box 558)
      - Gerding-Ballard precognition experiment, 1957-1958 (Box 559)
      - Ratte PK game experiment, 1959-1960 (Box 559)
      - Ratte ESP game experiments, 1960, (5 folders) (Box 559)
      - Ratte ESP game experiments, 1960, (2 folders) (Box 560)
      - Ratte game vs. standard PK, 1960, (5 folders) (Box 560)
      - CBC precognition test, 1961 (Box 560)
      - Lost man test correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 560)
      - Humm-Wadsworth temperament scale, undated (Box 561)
      - Series B data, undated (Box 561)
    - Rhine, L.
      - Misc. records, 1936-1938, (2 folders) (Box 561)
      - Dice PK, 1937 (Box 561)
      - Help-hinder experiments, 1942-1943, (4 folders) (Box 561)
    - Rhine, J.B. (Box 562)
      - Help-hinder experiments, 1942-1943, (2 folders) (Box 562)
      - LER-JBR 2 dice throwing “blind”, 1943 or 1944? (Box 562)
    - Rhine, S.
      - SLR-BMH Wright Refuge experiments, 1948, (5 folders) (Box 562)
      - SLR-BMH two agent experiments, 1951-1952, (5 folders) (Box 562)
      - SLR-BMH two agent experiments, 1951-1952, (9 folders) (Box 563)
      - SLR-BMC A-B-C experiment, 1952, (6 folders) (Box 563)
      - Correspondence with Maria, 1952 (Box 563)
      - Bea Weinstein data, 1952, (3 folders) (Box 563)
      - School for the Blind, 1953, (2 folders) (Box 564)
      - Weintraub clock ESP, 1953, (2 folders) (Box 564)
      - Anpsi abstracts, c. 1962 (Box 564)
      - Memory and ESP, 1963-1964 (Box 564)
      - Memory and ESP, 1963-1964 (Box 565)
      - “Consensus of Opinion” problem, undated (Box 565)
      - Miscellaneous data, undated, (4 folders) (Box 565)
      - Work at Wright Refuge, undated (Box 565)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 565)
    - Rivers, O.
      - Franklin Adams trials, 1948 (Box 565)
      - Wright Refuge series, 1948 (Box 565)
      - Mississippi State mental health study, 1948-1949, (3 folders) (Box 565)
      - Duke Hospital series, 1950 (Box 566)
      - Edgemont Community Center series, 1950, (3 folders) (Box 566)
      - Letter to J.B. Rhine, 1950 (Box 566)
      - Miscellaneous data, 1950, (3 folders) (Box 566)
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1950 (Box 566)
      - Mississippi State Hospital series, 1950, (2 folders) (Box 566)
      - Mississippi State Hospital series, 1950, (3 folders) (Box 567)
      - Raleigh series, 1950, (10 folders) (Box 567)
      - Raleigh series, 1950, (2 folders) (Box 568)
      - Miscellaneous studies, 1950-1951 (Box 568)
      - Three types of motivation, 1950-1951 (Box 568)
      - Mississippi State group ESP, 1951, (2 folders) (Box 568)
      - Starkville group ESP, 1951, (3 folders) (Box 568)
      - Starkville group ESP, 1951, (3 folders) (Box 569)
      - Symbols vs. animals, 1951 (Box 569)
      - Louisville experiment 2, 1952, (6 folders) (Box 569)
      - Miscellaneous ESP drawings, undated (Box 570)
      - Oxford series, undated (Box 570)
      - Precognition and GESP summaries, 1937 (Box 570)
      - Joseph's student research, 1937-1938 (Box 570)
      - Compartment box experiment, 1939 (Box 570)
      - Sealed envelopes experiment, 1939 (Box 570)
      - ESP experiment, 1940 (Box 570)
      - Name test experiment, 1940 (Box 570)
      - Correspondence tests, 1941 (Box 570)
      - Non-sealed box experiment, 1941 (Box 570)
      - P-value tests, 1941, (4 folders) (Box 570)
    - Russell, W. (Box 571)
      - P-value tests, 1941, (2 folders) (Box 571)
      - Scores independent check, undated (Box 571)
      - Precognition test, 1942 (Box 571)
    - Sattenstein Exploratory ESP and hypnosis, 1947 (Box 571)
    - Schmeidler, G.
      - Clairvoyance tests, 1946 (Box 571)
      - Clairvoyance drawings, 1948?, (4 folders) (Box 571)
      - Theison ESP, 1950 (Box 571)
      - ESP trials, undated (Box 571)
    - Skibinsky, M. (Box 572)
      - PK 12-1 series, 1948, (3 folders) (Box 572)
      - Mature vs. immature subjects, undated (Box 572)
      - Shuffled vs. unshuffled test, 1938, (2 folders) (Box 572)
      - Drug ESP series, 1938-1939, (2 folders) (Box 572)
      - ESP record sheets, 1938 (Box 572)
      - Factors affecting ESP, 1940? (Box 572)
      - Personal correspondence, 1940 (Box 572)
    - Smith, B. (Box 573)
      - Alcohol PK tests, 1946 (Box 573)
      - Classroom drawing experiment, 1947, (11 folders) (Box 573)
      - Questionnaire for palmists, undated (Box 573)
      - Position effects data, 1944 (Box 573)
    - Stone, C. Exploratory BM, 1944 (Box 574)
    - Stuart, C.
      - First tempo study, 1936 (Box 574)
      - Lag effect study, 1936 (Box 574)
      - Lab notebook, 1936-1937 (Box 574)
      - Parapsychological Notes, 1936-1937 (Box 574)
      - Miscellaneous data, 1936-1941, (7 folders) (Box 574)
      - Work with Martha Crocker, 1939 (Box 574)
      - Second tempo study, 1939-1941 (Box 574)
      - Pope Hill drawing tests, 1941, (3 folders) (Box 575)
      - Stanford academic affairs, 1942-1944, (16 folders) (Box 575)
      - Stanford correspondence, 1942-1944, (4 folders) (Box 575)
      - Stanford correspondence, 1942-1944, (5 folders) (Box 576)
      - Stanford illusion experiments, 1942-1944, (5 folders) (Box 576)
      - Stanford illusion experiments, 1942-1944, (8 folders) (Box 577)
      - Stanford Misc., 1942-1944, (7 folders) (Box 577)
      - Stanford Misc., 1942-1943, (15 folders) (Box 578)
      - Stanford Misc. data and analyses, 1942-1944, (5 folders) (Box 578)
      - Stanford Misc. data and analyses, 1942-1944, (13 folders) (Box 579)
      - Stanford Misc. data and analyses, 1942-1944, (12 folders) (Box 580)
      - Stanford series B, 1942-1944, (3 folders) (Box 580)
      - Stanford series D, 1942-1944, (5 folders) (Box 580)
      - Stanford series D, 1942-1944, (32 folders) (Box 581)
      - Stanford series DA, 1942-1944, (10 folders) (Box 581)
      - Stanford series DA, 1942-1944, (14 folders) (Box 582)
      - Stanford series H, 1942-1944, (44 folders) (Box 582)
      - Stanford series He, 1942-1944, (12 folders) (Box 583)
      - Stanford series N, 1942-1944, (11 folders) (Box 583)
      - Stanford series P, 1942-1944, (28 folders) (Box 583)
      - Stanford series Q, 1942-1944, (15 folders) (Box 584)
      - Stanford series R, 1942-1944, (4 folders) (Box 584)
      - Stanford series S, 1942-1944, (8 folders) (Box 584)
      - Stanford series S, 1942-1944, (38 folders) (Box 585)
      - Stanford series T1, 1942-1944, (2 folders) (Box 585)
      - Stanford series T1, 1942-1944, (2 folders) (Box 586)
      - Stanford series T2, 1942-1944, (17 folders) (Box 586)
      - Stanford series W, 1942-1944, (7 folders) (Box 586)
      - Stanford series, WS, 1942-194[?], (7 folders) (Box 587)
      - Stanford series Z, 1942-1944, (9 folders) (Box 587)
      - Corrington distance experiment, 1944, (5 folders) (Box 587)
      - DT-X series, 1945?, (3 folders) (Box 587)
      - DT-X series, 1945? (Box 588)
      - Late correspondence, 1945-1947, (3 folders) (Box 588)
      - Miscellaneous, 1945-1947, (17 folders) (Box 588)
      - Miscellaneous, 1945-1947, (3 folders) (Box 589)
      - Corington clairvoyance trials, 1946, (5 folders) (Box 589)
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 589)
      - Free-response targets, undated, (39 folders) (Box 589)
      - Miscellaneous, undated, (19 folders) (Box 590)
      - Miscellaneous, undated, (17 folders) (Box 591)
      - Miscellaneous, undated, (4 folders) (Box 592)
    - Sulloway, F. PK records, 1943-1944 (Box 592)
    - Sumner, F. ESP data, 1939-1940 (Box 592)
    - Turner, M.
      - George Killick data, 1949 (Box 592)
      - Atlanta-Durham distance precognition, 1951, (2 folders) (Box 592)
    - Urban-Kock
      - Electro-shock experiment, 1947-1950, (3 folders) (Box 592)
      - Electro-shock experiment, 1947-1950, (3 folders) (Box 593)
    - Van Busschbach
      - First American Series, 1956, (4 folders) (Box 593)
      - First American Series, 1956, (6 folders) (Box 594)
      - First American Series, 1956, (7 folders) (Box 595)
      - First American Series, 1956, (7 folders) (Box 596)
      - First American Series, 1956, (4 folders) (Box 597)
      - Second American Series, 1960, (3 folders) (Box 597)
      - Second American Series, 1960, (6 folders) (Box 598)
      - Second American Series, 1960, (6 folders) (Box 599)
      - Second American Series, 1960, (6 folders) (Box 600)
      - Second American Series, 1960, (2 folders) (Box 601)
    - Vasse, C.
      - Classroom GESP, 1955-1958 (Box 601)
      - PK with colored dice, 1958 (Box 601)
    - White, R.
      - Dual agent precognition test, 1955 (Box 601)
      - Emotionally charged symbols, 1955 (Box 601)
      - 5-Call experiment, 1955 (Box 601)
      - Fontaine experiment, 1955 (Box 601)
      - High-low experiment, 1955 (Box 601)
      - Hunger experiment, 1955 (Box 601)